g4s.com 2009-05-13

# G4S Privacy Policy

This privacy policy covers our use of the information collected by the G4S.com web site (or other linked G4S web sites) during your visit to our site.

## Cookies

G4S may store a small file (commonly known as a "cookie") on your computer when you visit G4S.com

We use cookies to improve our knowledge of the use of our web site and to help us determine how well our web site is operating.

The type of information we collect using cookies is specific to your PC and does not include personal information about you. We collect information such as the IP address, the date and time you visited the web site, which pages of our web sites you looked at and whether those web pages were delivered quickly and successfully.

Using this information allows us to improve our web site and to provide you a better online experience. 

You can delete our cookies or block this information by changing the settings on your PC (please refer to your browser’s help screens or instruction). If you block this information you may not be able to utilize some features of the site.

## Personal Information

We collect and use personal information (including name, address, telephone number and email) in order to:

  * respond to queries or requests submitted by you
  * provide services such as our Email Alert service
  * process orders or applications submitted by you
  * administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us
  * anticipate and resolve problems with any services supplied to you

We do not share this personal information with any other party.

## Visiting other sites

This policy applies to G4S.com.  However other G4S web sites may contain privacy policies which are different from this one. If you visit other G4S web sites please check the privacy policy of the site you visit.

We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other web sites even if: 

  * you accessed the third party web site using links from our web site; or 
  * you linked to our web site from a third party web site.

We recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact the owner or operator of such web site if you have any concerns or questions.

For more information about our privacy policy, please contact: [group.communications@g4s.com](mailto:group.communications@g4s.com)
